
Went from Mr. 305, Dade County, to Mr. Worldwide, all around the world Ay ay, yeah ah!
Now we're international, so international, international, so international,
You can't catch me, boy (can't catch me, boy)
I'm overseas and about a hundred G's per show
Don't test me, boy (don't test me, boy)
'Cause I rap with the best for sure,
305 'til the death of me
Cremate my body and let the ocean have what's left of me
But for now forget about that,
Blow the whistle
Baby, you're the referee
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep!
Wild like Los Angeles (Chris Brown)
My fantasy!
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat!
Oh, girl, it's international love (international)
Oh, yeah, it's international love
I don't play football but I've touched down everywhere.
Everywhere? Everywhere!
I don't play baseball but I've hit a home run everywhere, everywhere.
I've been to countries and cities I can't pronounce
And the places on the globe I didn't know existed.
In Romania she pulled me to the side and told me, "Pit, you can have me and my sister."
In Lebanon, yeah, the women are bomb
And in Greece—you've guessed it—the women are sweet.
Been all around the world but I ain't gon' lie–there's nothing like Miami's heat.
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep!
Wild like Los Angeles (A-ha)
My fantasy!
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat!
Ohh, girl, it's international love (international)
Ohh, yeah, it's international love
Down in D.R. they're looking for visas,
I ain't talking credit cards if you know what I mean!
En Cuba, la cosa esta dura!
But the woman get down, if you know what I mean!
In Colombia the women got everything done but they are some of the most beautiful women I've ever seen
In Brazil they're freaky with big old boobs and their thongs, blue yellow and green!
In L.A. tengo la Mexicana,
En New York tengo la boricua
Besito para todas las mujeres en Venezuela, muah!
Y en Miami tengo a cualquiera!
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep!
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy!
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat!
Oh (all around the world), it's international love (international)
Oh, yeah, it's international love
There's not a place that your love don't affect me, baby
So don't ever change
I'll cross the globe when I'm with you, baby
Hey, whoa-oh
Chris Brown, this is for the women worldwide
Let's rap
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep!
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy!
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat! (305)
Oh, yeah, it's international love (international, that's right)
Oh, yeah, it's international love
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep!
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy!
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat! (305)
Oh, yeah, it's international love (international)
Oh, yeah, it's international love
We're international, so international,
International, so international,
We're international, so international
International love
International love